pbsjdfirm.com 2002-12-07

# PBS&J Privacy Policy

**PBS &J is committed to your right to privacy and will make every effort to keep your personal information private. However, because our Web Site includes areas where the User can provide personally identifying information, we have developed the Privacy Policy below. The Policy will inform you of our practices and procedures regarding information that we may collect about you on this Site. If you have further questions about these practices and procedures after reading this Privacy Policy, please contact us.**

**This Privacy Policy governs all URL's hosted under the[www.pbsj.com](http://www.pbsj.com/) domain. PBS&J professionals control the information about you described in this document.**

**  
PBS &J Privacy Policy**

**1\. Information that we collect about you  
2\. Ways we collect information about you  
3\. Ways we use information about you  
4\. What information about you will be shared  
5\. Implications of collecting and sharing information about you  
6\. What you can do to control information collected about you**

**  
Additional Information**

**1\. Protection of children's online privacy on the pbsj.com domain  
2\. Changes to the pbsj.com domain Privacy Policy**

**  
1\. Information that we collect about you**

**PBS &J designs web sites that may collect and maintain certain personal information about you when you send us email or complete any of our online forms such as Feedback or Contact Us. This personal information can identify you and your business individually, and may include items such as your name and email address, job title, company name and address, phone number, web site address and contact details of the Web Site Administrator.**

**PBS &J also collects, or logs, certain other information that cannot personally identify you when you visit our Web Site. This information includes your Internet Protocol ("IP") address and your domain name. Your IP address is the number that is automatically assigned to your computer by the ISP computer through which you access the Web and your domain name is the name of the ISP computer itself through which you access the Web.**

**PBS &J logs these IP addresses and domain names and aggregates them for system administration and to monitor the use of our site. We use the aggregated information to measure the number of visits to our site, the average time spent on our site, the number of pages viewed, and various other site use statistics. This monitoring helps us to evaluate how our Web Site is used and to continuously improve the content we provide. While we may report aggregated IP address information to the Client who is paying for the Web Site hosting service, PBS&J does not link IP addresses or domain names with any personal information that can be used to identify the User. This means that a visitor's session will be logged on our servers, but the visitor will always remain anonymous.**

**PBS &J does not purchase or otherwise obtain any supplemental personal information about you from any third parties.**

**Back to top**

**2\. Ways we collect information about you**

**When you visit our Web Site, certain technical information (IP address and domain name) is automatically collected. We cannot use this technical information to identify you personally.**

**We also collect personal and company information that you provide to us via the Feedback Form, Contact Us form or other similar questionnaires.**

**If you have requested that we contact you regarding updated content for a specific web site, we may send you, via e-mail or post, our bi-weekly newsletter as well as other information impacting online customer relationships that we think you might find useful. If you do not wish to receive these communications please contact the webmaster for the designated site to request that we remove you from our mailing list. Alternatively, you may contact our corporate web master at[webmaster@pbsjis.com](mailto:webmaster@pbsjis.com)**

**We do not collect any information from you online other than the personal information described above. PBS &J does not use cookies to collect information about you for any reason.**

**Back to top**

**  
3\. Ways we use information about you**

**Any information you provide us will be used to contact you in response to any requests, complaints, or comments you may have about the Project or Web Site. If you have used our Contact Us form and have elected to join a mailing list, we may also use the information you have provided therein to contact you in the future regarding the Project or Web Site.**

**Back to top**

**4\. What information about you will be shared**

**Under certain circumstances, personal information that you have provided to us may be shared with the Client paying for the Web Site hosting. PBS &J does not collect or compile personal information for distribution to parties outside of PBS&J. Except as described below, PBS&J does not share any information about you with any parties outside of PBS&J.**

**If you send us email or use our Contact Us form to send us a request, complaint, or comment relating to any Web Site hosted under this domain, we may forward your request, complaint, or comment to the appropriate Web Site.**

**We will disclose personal information to comply with valid legal processes such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order, or to protect our rights and property. We will disclose information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.**

**Back to top**

**  
5\. Implications of collecting and sharing information about you**

**If you send us email or use our Contact Us form, we will send you an online acknowledgement that we have received your contact. If, when you complete our Contact Us form, you elect to join a mailing list, you may also receive other contact from us regarding other topics we feel may be of interest to you.**

**As previously mentioned above, under certain circumstances PBS &J may share personal information you provide us, such as your email address, job title or company name and address, with other service lines within PBS&J or the client paying for the web site hosting. These service lines may contact you, via email or post, to provide you information about their services and products that you may find useful.**

**Other than just mentioned, you will not receive any contact from third parties outside of PBS &J as a result of providing information to us, with the possible exception of contact from a web site to which we have forwarded a request, complaint, or comment that you have sent to us.**

**Back to top**

**  
6\. What you can do to control information collected about you**

**When you submit an inquiry, request, complaint, or comment to PBS &J you may have the opportunity to join a mailing list. If at a later time you wish to change your participation in our mailing list, please contact the webmaster for the designated site to send your request and our staff will make the appropriate change for you. Alternatively, you may contact our corporate web master at [webmaster@pbsjis.com](mailto:webmaster@pbsjis.com). You will receive confirmation that we have received your communication.**

**If you would like to update information previously submitted to PBS &J or request to have outdated information removed, please send your request through our Web site using the appropriate contact forms or email request options as these may vary from site to site..**

**Back to top**

**  
Additional Information**

**1\. Protection of children's online privacy on the PBSJ.com domain**

**PBS &J understands the importance of protecting children's privacy, especially in an online environment. PBS&J is not intentionally designed for or directed at children under 13 years of age. It is PBS&J's policy to never knowingly collect or maintain information about individuals under age 13.**

**Back to top**

**  
2\. Changes to the PBSJ.com domain Privacy Policy**

**PBS &J reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be preceded by a notice posted to this Privacy Policy at least ten (10) days prior to the effective date of such change.**

**Back to top**
